So after you have both your synch and asynch four club fountains together, you might want to think about switching in between them without stopping.
Now this is a pretty cool visual effect, but it will take a lot of time and a lot of practice.
So if you start with your asynch pattern, what you're going to do, is you're going to take your strong hand and you're going to throw a triple throw, and leave all other throws exactly the same.
So what this will do is it will delay your right hand by one beat, thereby putting it into the same pattern as your left and moving you into synchrous.
It looks something like this.
Here we're in asynch, we'll make a triple throw out of our left hand and keep all other throws the same, and it puts you into synch.
Now to get out of synch, to go back to asynch, you're going to do the exact same thing, you're going to delay your hand by one beat, but this will put you into asynch, just like that.
Hopefully you don't drop like I just did.
But again, so you can see how that works, we'll be in synch, a triple throw puts us right back into asynch.
Now that triple throw can be pretty hard to execute it sometimes, but you just have to really think about isolating your right and left hands, getting a triple and a double, and it should all work out!